<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ATD-Techknowledge</title>
    <description>Taking Advantage of Open Source in Your Learning Projects</description>
    <link>http://crichID.github.io/ATD-Techknowledge/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://crichID.github.io/ATD-Techknowledge/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2016 12:51:53 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2016 12:51:53 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Tragic Story</title>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;a-tragic-story&quot;&gt;A Tragic Story&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 2010, the US Government enacted a new law commonly known as &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cms.gov/openpayments/&quot;&gt;the Sunshine Act&lt;/a&gt;. It was designed to increase transparency in the financial relationships between health care providers and health care vendors. There are more than 6,500 medical device companies in the US. Every medical device company (and every pharma but let’s just stick with Med Device for now) was required to train their employees on the new reporting requirements.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;some-napkin-math&quot;&gt;Some Napkin Math&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just doing some rough calculations, let’s think about how much it cost to meet the mandatory training requirements of this new law:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;40 L&amp;amp;D Hours&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;15 Legal Hours&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;357,500 hours&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At an average of just $40 per hour that comes to $14,300,000 in the Medical Device sector alone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;lets-try-that-again&quot;&gt;Let’s Try That Again&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With Open Source, we could tell a different story.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s say 50 L&amp;amp;D leaders in the medical device industry got together and created an open source curriculum for the Sunshine Law.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Those 50 leaders spend 100 hours each. ($200,000)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Each company’s L&amp;amp;D spends 8 hours to customize and implement the training. ($2,080,000)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Legal only spends 3 hours to review. ($780,000)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With open source, the same training requirements are implemented for a total of $3,060,000.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;its-not-only-about-the-numbers&quot;&gt;It’s Not (Only) About the Numbers&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But let’s get away from the numbers for a minute; Of those 6,500 unique snowflakes - how many do you think were page turners? Boring? Ineffective? Let’s face it, those 6,500 L&amp;amp;D departments spent 80% of their effort getting the right words on the page.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once again, we can tell a different story with Open Source:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Open source creates a collaborative approach that improves outcomes.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Through open source, we can invert that effort and maximize results.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;We can also tap experts in a variety of fields. Need help with your Javascript?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;still-not-convinced&quot;&gt;Still Not Convinced?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If I can’t convince you, some of my (much smarter) colleagues have written extensively on the topic. Check out some of these resources:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ben.balter.com/2015/11/23/why-open-source/&quot;&gt;Why Open Source by Ben Balter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2016 11:31:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://crichID.github.io/ATD-Techknowledge/why-open</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://crichID.github.io/ATD-Techknowledge/why-open</guid>
        
        
        <category>open</category>
        
        <category>source</category>
        
        <category>activity</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>First Day On The Job</title>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;welcome-to-your-first-day-at-acme-inc&quot;&gt;Welcome to your first day at Acme, Inc.&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We realize you were probably expecting some sort of new hire orientation, but you are in training so we figured you didn’t need it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Performance reviews are due next week and all of our managers are complaining that they don’t know how to write a review. Can you put together a quick 2 hour class for tomorrow’s manager meeting to help them get started.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Forget all of that stuff you learned in about HPI and just write a class on basic principles of performance reviews.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Group 1: Icebreaker&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Group 2: Content&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Group 3: Application&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Group 4: Conclusion&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2016 11:30:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://crichID.github.io/ATD-Techknowledge/activity</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://crichID.github.io/ATD-Techknowledge/activity</guid>
        
        
        <category>open</category>
        
        <category>source</category>
        
        <category>activity</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
